A Guide to the Carl R. Fortney notebooks, 1964-1978
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Carl R. Fortney notebooks, 1964-1978
The Library of Virginia
41532
.7 cu. ft. and 2 boxes
Carl R. Fortney
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Jan Jennier of Bowie, Maryland.
Biographical Information
Carl R. Fortney was born 6 April 1915. He graduated from West Virginia University in 1937 with a degree in chemical engineering. He served as a captain in World War II. Fortney worked for the Virginia Department of Health. He and his wife Agnes had two children. Fortney died in Richmond, Virginia, 27 July 1986.
Scope and Content
Notebooks, 1964-1978, of Carl R. Fortney (1915-1986) of Richmond, Virginia, detailing his work for the Bureau of Industrial Hygiene, Virginia Department of Health, and consisting of addresses, clippings, contact information, flow charts, lists, maps, minutes, notes, reports, schematics, sketches, and loose papers. The notebooks contain his notes from inspections of various manufacturers, plants, businesses, and local health departments throughout Virginia. Includes some minutes for the Regional Air Pollution Advisory Board.
Contents List
- Notebook, 19 May 1964-4 June 1965 (Volume 1, Box 1)
- Notebook, 10 June 1965-26 January 1966 (Volume 2, Box 1)
- Notebook, 1 February 1966-11 May 1967 (Volume 3, Box 1)
- Notebook, 5 December 1966-30 June 1967 (Volume 4, Box 1)
- Notebook, 28 June 1967-8 January 1968 (Volume 5, Box 1)
- Notebook, 9 January 1968-5 September 1968 (Volume 6, Box 1)
- Notebook, 6 September 1968-6 February 1969 (Volume 7, Box 1)
- Notebook, 7 February 1969-27 June 1969 (Volume 8, Box 1)
- Notebook, 8 July 1969-18 February 1970 (Volume 9, Box 1)
- Notebook, 3 March 1970-25 September 1970 (Volume 10, Box 2)
- Notebook, 8 October 1970-27 May 1971 (Volume 11, Box 2)
- Notebook, 2 June 1971-9 August 1973 (Volume 12, Box 2)
- Notebook, 4 December 1973-18 October 1974 (Volume 13, Box 2)
- Notebook, 24 October 1974-5 May 1976 (Volume 14, Box 2)
- Notebook, 7 May 1976-28 December 1978 (Volume 15, Box 2)
- Notebook, 4 March 1968-10 November 1970 (Volume A, Box 2)
- Notebook, 13 November 1970-15 November 1973 (Volume B, Box 2)
- Notebook, 10 December 1973-28 March 1977 (Volume C, Box 2)